<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aurreum</title>
    <link>https://www.aurreum.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aurreum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aurreum.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aurreum SAP IQ&#39;s streaming backup data protection solution makes a stunning debut!</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-16/</guid>
      <description>Limitations of traditional backup
The traditional backup solution for SAP IQ typically involves the use of specific backup scripts. In this approach, the backup data is first cached locally on the database server and then transferred to the designated backup storage media.
This backup solution has the following limitations, which makes it difficult to improve backup performance and handle large-scale business scenarios:
  High risk: Manually writing or modifying backup scripts is prone to errors, and maintenance becomes challenging as versions evolve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from a Cloud Service Provider&#39;s Data Deletion Incident: Backup Responsibility Lies Beyond the Cloud Service Provider</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-15/</guid>
      <description>Recently, an incident involving a globally renowned cloud computing provider mistakenly deleting a fund company&amp;rsquo;s private cloud account has garnered significant attention. This mistake led to hundreds of thousands of the fund company&amp;rsquo;s members being unable to access their retirement accounts for seven days, causing considerable anxiety among users.
Although the fund company had deployed redundant services in two different regions to ensure easy recovery in case of service failure or data loss, this incident deleted the company&amp;rsquo;s cloud subscription, resulting in the loss of backup data in both regions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data deduplication: maximizing backup cost-effectiveness!</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-14/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t underestimate it; data deduplication is crucial in enterprise backup applications. It&amp;rsquo;s like a magic wand that eliminates redundant data, saving substantial storage space for businesses while ensuring the integrity and consistency of backup data. This directly impacts the economic efficiency of backup systems!
When selecting a backup platform, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to focus on the data deduplication function. Data deduplication serves as the foundation of backup systems and constitutes the core capability of the product!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MySQL Continuous Log Real-time Protection (CLRP), achieving a sub-second RPO is not a dream!</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-13/</guid>
      <description>Traditional MySQL database backup methods suffer from serious data loss. When a production host fails, users can only restore to the most recent backup point, which may result in several hours or even days of data loss. In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven era, data has become a critical element of production. Therefore, more advanced technology is needed to ensure data security.
To address the shortcomings of traditional backup methods, Aurreum has independently developed the Continuous Log Real-time Protection (CLRP) technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is data recovery considered the new frontier in combating ransomware?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-12/</guid>
      <description>Ransomware has become one of the most serious cybersecurity threats today as attackers target individuals, businesses, and government entities. Cybercriminals encrypt crucial data and demand substantial ransoms, causing operational disruption and significant financial and reputational losses. In the past, some ransomware attacks made headlines, but unfortunately, the threat from ransomware has evolved into a reality that nearly every enterprise must face. Reports show that 85% of businesses experienced at least one ransomware attack last year, with roughly half of them enduring two to three attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Choose an Outstanding Cloud Backup Service Provider</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-11/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, data backup has become a critical operational element for businesses. Selecting an excellent cloud backup service provider is crucial to ensure data security, efficient backups, and swift data recovery. This article will provide a detailed guide on choosing a reliable cloud backup service, covering key factors such as performance, efficiency, security, reliability, cost, feature depth, data migration capability, geographical coverage, and availability.
Performance: When selecting a cloud backup service provider, one of the primary considerations is performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Backup and Recovery — An Effective Antidote Against Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-10/</guid>
      <description>Aurreum delivers unmatched ransomware protection and resilience. The following text will introduce real-life scenarios of how the Aurreum product is used by enterprises to defend against ransomware.
Ransomware, a prevalent and powerful type of malware equipped with robust encryption capabilities, often infiltrates target computers through methods like phishing and exploiting vulnerabilities. It implants malicious programs through tactics such as phishing and vulnerability exploits, subsequently attacking by encrypting or destroying files and even all data on the disk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking the Initiative to Counteract Ransomware: Proactive Protection</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-09/</guid>
      <description>Faced with the increasing severity of cybersecurity threats, businesses have come to realize that data is their most valuable asset, regardless of their size or industry. The true value of data can only be harnessed through effective protective measures that drive business innovation and development. Hence, data protection is of utmost importance.
Aurreum believes that a comprehensive ransomware strategy should encompass both reducing the risk of successful attacks and mitigating the impact of such attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seizing Opportunities in Data Management Challenges: Aurreum&#39;s Contribution to CDM</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-07/</guid>
      <description>Data management has presented distinct characteristics in five dimensions compared to the past. Firstly, there has been a rapid expansion in scale, with even regular relational databases reaching capacities in the terabyte range, and larger ones reaching 100TB or even several hundred terabytes. Secondly, the volume of data access has surged due to the internet-driven application landscape, resulting in larger user bases and more frequent data retrieval and updates. Thirdly, the importance of data security has become more pronounced as data has become a core asset for enterprises, serving as the foundation for their survival and growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Data Backup with Deduplication Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-08/</guid>
      <description>Data backup is a crucial component of modern information technology. With the continuous growth of data volume and increasing demands for data protection, traditional backup methods have encountered challenges such as insufficient storage space and lengthy backup times. To address these issues, deduplication technology has emerged as a solution. Deduplication technology is a data reduction method that identifies and removes duplicate data, enabling efficient data backup and storage. In this article, we will explore the application of deduplication technology in data backup and the benefits it brings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can we double the backup speed of a massive number of small files?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-06/</guid>
      <description>With the increasingly improved management of information technology in industries such as healthcare, education, e-commerce, and finance, there are also more types of unstructured data, including records (schools, libraries), images (e-commerce), videos (hospitals), bills (finance), drawings (design companies), and more. The amount of data in enterprises has grown exponentially from gigabytes (GB) to terabytes (TB) and even petabytes (PB). Within this massive amount of data, there are often numerous small files, with individual file sizes below kilobytes (KB), but the number of files can reach millions, tens of millions, or even billions, resulting in a massive volume of small files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aurreum&#39;s Continuous Log Real-time Protection (CLRP) technology - achieving sub-second RPO is not a dream</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-04/</guid>
      <description>How to reduce the RPO to sub-second level for backup and recovery of Oracle databases?
How to achieve real-time data replication while minimizing resource consumption?
Aurreum&amp;rsquo;s Continuous Log Real-time Protection (CLRP) technology effortlessly addresses these challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the advantages and principles behind this technology:
It is well-known that Oracle database backups are typically performed using the RMAN backup tool. However, RMAN can only back up data files and archived logs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embracing the Advantages of Enterprise Cloud Backup</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-05/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven world, the importance of reliable data backup and recovery cannot be overstated. Enterprises of all sizes face the risk of data loss due to various factors, including hardware failures, natural disasters, human errors, or malicious attacks. To mitigate these risks, many organizations are turning to enterprise cloud backup solutions. Cloud backup offers numerous advantages over traditional backup methods, providing enhanced data protection, scalability, cost-effectiveness, and peace of mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-ransomware case: 12 Hours of Thrilling Stars</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-03/</guid>
      <description>The following is a real ransomware attack and successful recovery story: An educational institution faced a thrilling ransomware attack and rescued the production system in 12 hours.
In recent years, the educational institution&amp;rsquo;s data volume has exploded. Especially in the past three years, the growth rate has been as high as nearly ten times. As the amount of data continues to grow, the organization faces the hidden worry of efficiency and performance impact during the expansion of the backup system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attacks: How to Stay Calm and Protect Your Data?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-02/</guid>
      <description>Ransomware has become a major cyber threat to businesses and organizations worldwide. The United States has become the number one target area for ransomware attacks due to the gap between the data protection measures of many local companies and their digital transformation. The complex IT environment brought by the hybrid multi-cloud era has further provided a breeding ground for ransomware. As a result, an unsuspecting ransomware attack can cause unplanned downtime and irreversible damage to business and reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aurreum released the industry&#39;s most reliable cloud data management platform</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-01/</guid>
      <description>The breakout innovator Aurreum International has just released its Cloud Data Protection Service. Built from the ground up by the engineers of Aurreum, the Cloud Data Protection Service aims to bring effective multi-cloud data management tools to IT professionals of small businesses and enterprises. This service will help enterprises effectively protect data in the cloud, avoid data loss, defend against ransomware attacks, and achieve simple and unified cloud data management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AURREUM End User License Agreement (EULA)</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/user-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/user-agreement/</guid>
      <description>Important Notice This Agreement is an End User License Agreement (“EULA”) regarding the use of the Software (as defined in Section 1.1 of this Agreement) between you (an individual, company, or any other entity) and AURREUM. Please read this Agreement carefully and accept it before using your AURREUM products or downloading the software updates attached to this Agreement. Once you use AURREUM products or download this software updates, you will be deemed to have fully agreed to and bound by the terms of this Agreement, including acceptance of any changes made by AURREUM to the terms of this Agreement at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/privacy-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/privacy-notice/</guid>
      <description>AURREUM takes your privacy very seriously. We will take appropriate security measures to protect your personal information in accordance with the requirements of laws and regulations. This Notice is designed to help you understand what information we collect or process about you and what we do with this information when you use AURREUM&amp;rsquo;s products.
Before using AURREUM&amp;rsquo;s products or services, please read and understand this Notice carefully. Your use of products or services of AURREUM will indicate that you have fully understood and agreed to this Notice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/company/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/company/</guid>
      <description>Our Vision We are one world. We seek to create a safe world without artificial barriers or imposed limitations. As humans, we have come from cave paintings to digital arts previously unimaginable. Although what requires protection in our lives has changed, the significance of protecting what is precious has not. Global customers trust Aurreum to safeguard their digital treasures from a wide range of threats, including (not limited to) hardware failures, natural disasters, human mistakes, and cyber-attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Us We are always open and we welcome questions you have for our team. If you wish to get in touch, please fill out the form below. Someone from our team will get back to you shortly.
 Your Name*    Your Email*     Your Phone    Your Company     Your Message*     SEND          aurreum@aurreum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/download/detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/download/detail/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/my-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/my-account/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/partners/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/products/acdps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/products/acdps/</guid>
      <description>Concerned about the data loss of your local computer due to accidents, hardware failures, or human mistakes? Afraid of ransomware attacks? Unease about your cloud data due to the rising number of data center disasters?
We&#39;ve got your back. Aurreum provides a managed cloud data protection service for businesses of any size, anywhere, and any time. Backing up your valuable business data in hybrid clouds, Aurreum can quickly bring your IT service online through cloud-based instant recovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/products/adpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/products/adpa/</guid>
      <description>From large corporations that colocate their servers in a data center to small businesses that do not even have a server room, Aurreum provides a turnkey data protection solution for businesses of any size.
  DEMO     DATA SHEET          Easy Setup  Rack the appliance, power up, and within minutes Aurreum data protection suite will be up and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/products/adps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/products/adps/</guid>
      <description>Your ubiquitous data is your most valuable asset. Protect it! As the most valuable resource for businesses in the interconnected era, data can help a company meaningfully engage with customers, make business decisions, add value to the organization, and better inform product and service development. Losing valuable data may cause the business to flounder and even shutdown.
Aurreum Data Protection Suite (ADPS) integrates backup/restore, disaster recovery, replication, Continuous Data Protection (CDP), Copy Data Management (CDM), and Bare Metal Recovery (BMR) into a single unified platform to address the data protection needs of all businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/questions/001-refund/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/questions/001-refund/</guid>
      <description>If you want to request a refund on your CDPS subscription, please email admin@aurreum.com with the following information:
 Your name and telephone Order No. and purchase date Your Aurreum account email address Refund reason  We will process your refund request as soon as possible after we receive your email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/trial-apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/trial-apply/</guid>
      <description>    Your Aurreum Cloud Data Protection Service trial is almost ready!  In this video, you&#39;ll learn about how to use CDPS to protect your data.        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/trial/</guid>
      <description>FREE Trial now Start your free 30-day trial with Aurreum expert support  Company *   Name *         Email *   Phone *         State * Please select    Yes, I want to receive information about Aurreum products and events. I understand that I can unsubscribe at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/video-animation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/video-animation/</guid>
      <description>   3-minute overview
Getting familiar with Aurreum Data Protection Suite can help you to start fast. In this video, you&#39;ll learn about the product capabilities and all the benefits you can gain from ADPS.
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/video/</guid>
      <description>   In this 7-minute video, we will introduce how to back up and restore files with Aurreum Data Protection Suite (ADPS).
We will cover:
How to install the file agent.
How to activate the resource and authorize user access.
How to create a file backup job.
How to create a file restore job.
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>001-adps</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/001-adps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/001-adps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>002-adps-demo</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/002-adps-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/002-adps-demo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>003-adpa-ds</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/003-adpa-ds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/003-adpa-ds/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>004-adpa-white-paper</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/004-adpa-white-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/004-adpa-white-paper/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>005-adps-agent_install</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/005-adps-agent_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/005-adps-agent_install/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>006-adps-oracle</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/006-adps-oracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/006-adps-oracle/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>007-adps-mysql</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/007-adps-mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/007-adps-mysql/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>008-adps-mssql</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/008-adps-mssql/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/008-adps-mssql/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>009-adps-file</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/009-adps-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/009-adps-file/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>010-adps-vmware</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/010-adps-vmware/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/010-adps-vmware/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>011-adps-manager</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/011-adps-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/011-adps-manager/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>012-adps-install</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/012-adps-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/012-adps-install/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>013-adps-hyper-v</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/013-adps-hyper-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/013-adps-hyper-v/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>014-adps-postgres</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/014-adps-postgres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/014-adps-postgres/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>015-adps-sybase</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/015-adps-sybase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/015-adps-sybase/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>016-adps-obs</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/016-adps-obs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/016-adps-obs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>017-adps-cachedb</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/017-adps-cachedb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/017-adps-cachedb/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>018-adps-db2</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/018-adps-db2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/018-adps-db2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>019-adps-hana</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/019-adps-hana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/019-adps-hana/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>020-adps-informix</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/020-adps-informix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/020-adps-informix/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>021-adps-linux-os</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/021-adps-linux-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/021-adps-linux-os/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>022-adps-mongodb</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/022-adps-mongodb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/022-adps-mongodb/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>023-adps-mariadb</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/023-adps-mariadb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/023-adps-mariadb/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>024-adps-hadoop</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/024-adps-hadoop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/024-adps-hadoop/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>025-adps-exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/025-adps-exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/025-adps-exchange/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>026-adpa-iso-installation-guide</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/026-adpa-iso-installation-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/026-adpa-iso-installation-guide/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>027-adps-openstack</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/027-adps-openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/027-adps-openstack/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>028-adps-k8s</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/028-adps-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/028-adps-k8s/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>029-adps-ndmp</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/029-adps-ndmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/029-adps-ndmp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>030-adps-sap-iq</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/030-adps-sap-iq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/030-adps-sap-iq/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>031-adps-sap-ase</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/031-adps-sap-ase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/031-adps-sap-ase/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>032-adps-exchange-online</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/032-adps-exchange-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/032-adps-exchange-online/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>033-adps-sharepoint</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/033-adps-sharepoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/resource/033-adps-sharepoint/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
