<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aurreum</title>
    <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aurreum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aurreum.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Data Backup, Synchronization, Archiving, and Migration</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-35/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital economy, data is the backbone of every business. From financial records to customer information, from app data to design files-losing it can mean losing trust, revenue, or even your company&amp;rsquo;s reputation. Yet terms like backup, synchronization, archiving, and migration often get mixed up. They may sound similar, but each plays a very different role in protecting and managing your data. Let&amp;rsquo;s break it down.
1. Data Backup What it is:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to the Cloud ≠ Absolute Safety</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-34/</guid>
      <description>Why Shared Responsibility Doesn&amp;rsquo;t Mean Full Protection Have you ever heard someone say this?
&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, our data is already on the cloud. What could possibly go wrong?&amp;rdquo;
But when something does go wrong, reality hits hard:
 No one is liable for your lost data. Worse, you might not be able to recover it.  Cloud providers secure the infrastructure, but you are responsible for the safety of your data-its privacy, integrity, and recoverability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Data Protection, the Real Risk Isn&#39;t &#39;No Backup&#39; - It&#39;s &#39;Backup That Can&#39;t Be Recovered&#39;</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-33/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to data protection, what&amp;rsquo;s the worst nightmare for an enterprise?
Not &amp;ldquo;no backup&amp;rdquo;, but rather:
Thinking you have a backup only to find it can&amp;rsquo;t be restored. In recent years, many organizations have been drawn to a buzzword in the disaster recovery space:
CDP - Continuous Data Protection. Vendors often market CDP with slogans like:
 Microsecond-level protection! Rollback anytime! Instantly recover from accidental deletions! Restore to any point in time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Deduplication and Intelligent Compression: How to Protect More with Less Storage</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-32/</guid>
      <description>As enterprises accelerate their digital transformation, data is growing at an exponential rate. Files, databases, VM snapshots, logs, user activity records-data accumulates by the minute. At the same time, the demand for robust data protection is rising:
&amp;ldquo;We need to back up everything, recover it fast, isolate it safely-and do it all with less cost.&amp;rdquo;
This is where data deduplication and intelligent compression come into play. These technologies allow organizations to store less while protecting more-efficiently and intelligently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Isolation and Recovery Control in Multi-Tenant Environments: Can You Really Keep &#39;Other People&#39;s Data&#39; Safe?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-31/</guid>
      <description>As cloud computing, big data platforms, and SaaS services become mainstream, multi-tenant architecture has emerged as a cost-effective and scalable solution for serving multiple customers or internal business units. But with shared infrastructure comes a pressing question:
When data from different tenants resides on the same system, can you truly ensure that each tenant&amp;rsquo;s data remains separate, secure, and recoverable?
That’s where data isolation and recovery control in multi-tenant environments becomes critical—not just for compliance, but for trust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup vs. Archiving: Do You Really Understand the Difference?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-30/</guid>
      <description>In today’s data-driven world, protecting business data is non-negotiable. Yet, many confuse backup and archiving, two critical but distinct data management practices. Understanding their differences is key to ensuring your business meets both operational and compliance needs. In this article, we’ll clarify what sets backup and archiving apart, why both matter, and how Aurreum’s data protection solutions can help.
What is Backup? A backup is a copy of your active data, created to enable quick recovery in case of data loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Common Data Backup Mistakes—Are You Guilty?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-29/</guid>
      <description>Data is the lifeblood of modern businesses, and backing it up is a non-negotiable step to protect it. Yet, even with the best intentions, companies often fall into traps that undermine their data protection efforts. These mistakes can leave you vulnerable to data loss, downtime, or costly recovery efforts. Here are five common backup mistakes businesses make—and how to avoid them.
1. Skipping Regular Backup Testing Problem: You’ve set up a backup system—great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Choose the Right Backup Solution for Your Business?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-28/</guid>
      <description>In today’s digital world, data is the backbone of every business. Whether it’s customer records, financial data, or operational files, losing it can spell disaster. Choosing a backup solution isn’t just about having one—it’s about picking the right one. A well-suited backup plan ensures data security while aligning with your budget and efficiency needs. So, how do you make the best choice? Here are key steps to guide you.
1. Understand Your Backup Needs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Supercomputers Are Booming, But Is Your Data Safe? How to Protect Against Loss and Attacks?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-27/</guid>
      <description>Recently, AI supercomputers have taken the tech world by storm, driving a massive wave of interest in AI Supercomputers. More and more companies and research institutions are deploying AI models locally to reduce computational costs, improve efficiency, and safeguard data privacy and compliance. But here’s the problem:
Is the data in your AI supercomputer really safe?
Imagine this—if a hardware failure, program error, system crash, or, worse yet, a ransomware attack occurs, your AI training and inference could be halted in an instant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-2-1 Backup Rule: The Best Practice to Ensure Data Integrity</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-26/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven world, data is not only the core asset for businesses but also an indispensable part of personal lives. Whether it is a company&amp;rsquo;s financial records or an individual&amp;rsquo;s photos and documents, data loss can lead to irreversible consequences. Therefore, ensuring the safety and reliability of data is more critical than ever.
Why is Backup So Important?
The risks of data loss are everywhere. Hard drive failures, cyberattacks, natural disasters, and even human errors can all lead to data corruption or loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reducing IT Management Costs: Simplified and Intelligent Data Management with Aurreum</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-25/</guid>
      <description>In today’s digitally-driven business environment, enterprises are increasingly dependent on data, while facing escalating costs and complex management challenges. With rapidly growing data volumes, traditional storage and management methods have become cumbersome and inefficient. Aurreum leverages its intelligent and automated data protection platform to provide businesses with a streamlined and effective solution, making data protection more accessible and cost-effective while significantly reducing IT management expenses.
Challenges in Data Management
As businesses operate in hybrid cloud environments, across multiple operating systems, and with various workloads, the complexity of managing data has dramatically increased:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Data Management: End-to-End Protection from Cloud to On-Premises with Aurreum</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-24/</guid>
      <description>In an era where data drives business success, organizations increasingly rely on hybrid environments combining cloud services and on-premises infrastructure. While this approach offers flexibility and scalability, it also introduces challenges in managing, protecting, and recovering data across diverse platforms. To address these complexities, Aurreum provides a cutting-edge, end-to-end data management solution that ensures seamless protection and accessibility, no matter where your data resides.
The Challenges of Hybrid Data Environments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Security for SMEs: Aurreum&#39;s Accessible Solution</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-23/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced digital world, data has become the core asset for businesses of all sizes. However, with the rise of ransomware, data breaches, and data loss, data security is no longer a “luxury” exclusive to large corporations. Small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) must also prioritize data protection to ensure sustainable growth. Yet, SMEs often face unique challenges in data protection due to budget constraints, limited technical resources, and lack of specialized personnel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup testing and verification: the last line of defense for enterprise data security</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-22/</guid>
      <description>In the digital age, data has become one of the most important assets for businesses. Data loss or corruption can lead to business disruption, financial loss, and even legal risks. Therefore, data backup has become a crucial means of protecting key enterprise data. However, many businesses tend to focus solely on completing backups while neglecting the testing and verification of backup data. In fact, testing and verifying backups is the key to ensuring that data is truly recoverable, making it the last line of defense for enterprise data security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CDM technology: Aurreum&#39;s new tool for revolutionizing data protection</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-21/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven era, efficiently protecting and managing vast amounts of data presents a major challenge for enterprises. Traditional backup methods, such as periodic full backups combined with incremental backups, often fall short in the big data era. These methods can lead to prolonged backup durations, excessive resource consumption, and complicated recovery processes. To address these challenges, Aurreum has introduced the innovative Copy Data Management (CDM) technology.
Advantages of Aurreum&amp;rsquo;s CDM technology</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup and disaster recovery: the ultimate safeguard for enterprise security</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-20/</guid>
      <description>Background of backup and disaster recovery
In 1993, the World Trade Center in the United States experienced a terrorist bombing incident that shocked the world. At the time of the incident, approximately 350 companies operated within the World Trade Center. However, just one year later, that number had dwindled to 150. The remaining 200 companies faced bankruptcy because they could not recover their crucial data and information systems. This disaster vividly demonstrates the importance of data and IT systems to the survival of enterprises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Microsoft Blue Screen of Death incident: A wake-up call for enterprise data security</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-19/</guid>
      <description>On July 19th, a massive global outage struck Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows operating system, sweeping multiple countries and regions like a sudden storm. From the United States to Japan, from the UK to India, countless public services, financial transaction networks, and aviation systems were severely impacted, with some experiencing temporary disruptions. This incident, dubbed &amp;ldquo;Microsoft Blue Screen of Death,&amp;rdquo; topped trending charts worldwide quickly, sparking widespread panic and chaos.
The catastrophic impact of the Microsoft Blue Screen of Death incident</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aurreum database replication family welcomes a new member, MySQL data security protection upgraded</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-18/</guid>
      <description>Aurreum database replication supports Oracle and SQL Server databases, offering a wide range of data security protection capabilities from logical backups, physical backups, and synthetic backups to continuous log real-time protection and remote disaster recovery.
To cater to more application scenarios and data restore requirements, Aurreum has officially launched a new database replication feature specifically for MySQL, providing more diverse protection capabilities. It offers a flexible, reliable, and secure data protection solution for users&#39; business systems, establishing an impregnable data security defense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive strategies for tackling VMware snapshot residue: Aurreum&#39;s virtualization backup solution</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-17/</guid>
      <description>VMware&amp;rsquo;s snapshot feature has long been considered a convenient tool for data backup. However, over time, snapshot residue has become a thorny issue in the field of backup and disaster recovery. If the snapshot residue is not properly handled, it can lead to abnormal business environments, data leaks, and even compliance issues. To address this pain point, Aurreum offers a comprehensive and efficient solution from the pre-backup, in-backup, and post-backup stages, providing enterprises with granular management of their virtual machine backups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aurreum SAP IQ&#39;s streaming backup data protection solution makes a stunning debut!</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-16/</guid>
      <description>Limitations of traditional backup
The traditional backup solution for SAP IQ typically involves the use of specific backup scripts. In this approach, the backup data is first cached locally on the database server and then transferred to the designated backup storage media.
This backup solution has the following limitations, which makes it difficult to improve backup performance and handle large-scale business scenarios:
  High risk: Manually writing or modifying backup scripts is prone to errors, and maintenance becomes challenging as versions evolve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from a cloud service provider&#39;s data deletion incident: Backup responsibility lies beyond the cloud service provider</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-15/</guid>
      <description>Recently, an incident involving a globally renowned cloud computing provider mistakenly deleting a fund company&amp;rsquo;s private cloud account has garnered significant attention. This mistake led to hundreds of thousands of the fund company&amp;rsquo;s members being unable to access their retirement accounts for seven days, causing considerable anxiety among users.
Although the fund company had deployed redundant services in two different regions to ensure easy recovery in case of service failure or data loss, this incident deleted the company&amp;rsquo;s cloud subscription, resulting in the loss of backup data in both regions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data deduplication: maximizing backup cost-effectiveness!</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-14/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t underestimate it; data deduplication is crucial in enterprise backup applications. It&amp;rsquo;s like a magic wand that eliminates redundant data, saving substantial storage space for businesses while ensuring the integrity and consistency of backup data. This directly impacts the economic efficiency of backup systems!
When selecting a backup platform, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to focus on the data deduplication function. Data deduplication serves as the foundation of backup systems and constitutes the core capability of the product!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MySQL Continuous Log Real-time Protection (CLRP), achieving a sub-second RPO is not a dream!</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-13/</guid>
      <description>Traditional MySQL database backup methods suffer from serious data loss. When a production host fails, users can only restore to the most recent backup point, which may result in several hours or even days of data loss. In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven era, data has become a critical element of production. Therefore, more advanced technology is needed to ensure data security.
To address the shortcomings of traditional backup methods, Aurreum has independently developed the Continuous Log Real-time Protection (CLRP) technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is data recovery considered the new frontier in combating ransomware?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-12/</guid>
      <description>Ransomware has become one of the most serious cybersecurity threats today as attackers target individuals, businesses, and government entities. Cybercriminals encrypt crucial data and demand substantial ransoms, causing operational disruption and significant financial and reputational losses. In the past, some ransomware attacks made headlines, but unfortunately, the threat from ransomware has evolved into a reality that nearly every enterprise must face. Reports show that 85% of businesses experienced at least one ransomware attack last year, with roughly half of them enduring two to three attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Choose an Outstanding Cloud Backup Service Provider</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-11/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, data backup has become a critical operational element for businesses. Selecting an excellent cloud backup service provider is crucial to ensure data security, efficient backups, and swift data recovery. This article will provide a detailed guide on choosing a reliable cloud backup service, covering key factors such as performance, efficiency, security, reliability, cost, feature depth, data migration capability, geographical coverage, and availability.
Performance: When selecting a cloud backup service provider, one of the primary considerations is performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Backup and Recovery — An Effective Antidote Against Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-10/</guid>
      <description>Aurreum delivers unmatched ransomware protection and resilience. The following text will introduce real-life scenarios of how the Aurreum product is used by enterprises to defend against ransomware.
Ransomware, a prevalent and powerful type of malware equipped with robust encryption capabilities, often infiltrates target computers through methods like phishing and exploiting vulnerabilities. It implants malicious programs through tactics such as phishing and vulnerability exploits, subsequently attacking by encrypting or destroying files and even all data on the disk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking the Initiative to Counteract Ransomware: Proactive Protection</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-09/</guid>
      <description>Faced with the increasing severity of cybersecurity threats, businesses have come to realize that data is their most valuable asset, regardless of their size or industry. The true value of data can only be harnessed through effective protective measures that drive business innovation and development. Hence, data protection is of utmost importance.
Aurreum believes that a comprehensive ransomware strategy should encompass both reducing the risk of successful attacks and mitigating the impact of such attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seizing Opportunities in Data Management Challenges: Aurreum&#39;s Contribution to CDM</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-07/</guid>
      <description>Data management has presented distinct characteristics in five dimensions compared to the past. Firstly, there has been a rapid expansion in scale, with even regular relational databases reaching capacities in the terabyte range, and larger ones reaching 100TB or even several hundred terabytes. Secondly, the volume of data access has surged due to the internet-driven application landscape, resulting in larger user bases and more frequent data retrieval and updates. Thirdly, the importance of data security has become more pronounced as data has become a core asset for enterprises, serving as the foundation for their survival and growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Data Backup with Deduplication Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-08/</guid>
      <description>Data backup is a crucial component of modern information technology. With the continuous growth of data volume and increasing demands for data protection, traditional backup methods have encountered challenges such as insufficient storage space and lengthy backup times. To address these issues, deduplication technology has emerged as a solution. Deduplication technology is a data reduction method that identifies and removes duplicate data, enabling efficient data backup and storage. In this article, we will explore the application of deduplication technology in data backup and the benefits it brings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can we double the backup speed of a massive number of small files?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-06/</guid>
      <description>With the increasingly improved management of information technology in industries such as healthcare, education, e-commerce, and finance, there are also more types of unstructured data, including records (schools, libraries), images (e-commerce), videos (hospitals), bills (finance), drawings (design companies), and more. The amount of data in enterprises has grown exponentially from gigabytes (GB) to terabytes (TB) and even petabytes (PB). Within this massive amount of data, there are often numerous small files, with individual file sizes below kilobytes (KB), but the number of files can reach millions, tens of millions, or even billions, resulting in a massive volume of small files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aurreum&#39;s Continuous Log Real-time Protection (CLRP) technology - achieving sub-second RPO is not a dream</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-04/</guid>
      <description>How to reduce the RPO to sub-second level for backup and recovery of Oracle databases?
How to achieve real-time data replication while minimizing resource consumption?
Aurreum&amp;rsquo;s Continuous Log Real-time Protection (CLRP) technology effortlessly addresses these challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the advantages and principles behind this technology:
It is well-known that Oracle database backups are typically performed using the RMAN backup tool. However, RMAN can only back up data files and archived logs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embracing the Advantages of Enterprise Cloud Backup</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-05/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven world, the importance of reliable data backup and recovery cannot be overstated. Enterprises of all sizes face the risk of data loss due to various factors, including hardware failures, natural disasters, human errors, or malicious attacks. To mitigate these risks, many organizations are turning to enterprise cloud backup solutions. Cloud backup offers numerous advantages over traditional backup methods, providing enhanced data protection, scalability, cost-effectiveness, and peace of mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-ransomware case: 12 Hours of Thrilling Stars</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-03/</guid>
      <description>The following is a real ransomware attack and successful recovery story: An educational institution faced a thrilling ransomware attack and rescued the production system in 12 hours.
In recent years, the educational institution&amp;rsquo;s data volume has exploded. Especially in the past three years, the growth rate has been as high as nearly ten times. As the amount of data continues to grow, the organization faces the hidden worry of efficiency and performance impact during the expansion of the backup system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attacks: How to Stay Calm and Protect Your Data?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-02/</guid>
      <description>Ransomware has become a major cyber threat to businesses and organizations worldwide. The United States has become the number one target area for ransomware attacks due to the gap between the data protection measures of many local companies and their digital transformation. The complex IT environment brought by the hybrid multi-cloud era has further provided a breeding ground for ransomware. As a result, an unsuspecting ransomware attack can cause unplanned downtime and irreversible damage to business and reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aurreum released the industry&#39;s most reliable cloud data management platform</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-01/</guid>
      <description>The breakout innovator Aurreum International has just released its Cloud Data Protection Service. Built from the ground up by the engineers of Aurreum, the Cloud Data Protection Service aims to bring effective multi-cloud data management tools to IT professionals of small businesses and enterprises. This service will help enterprises effectively protect data in the cloud, avoid data loss, defend against ransomware attacks, and achieve simple and unified cloud data management.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
