<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aurreum</title>
    <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aurreum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aurreum.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attacks: How to Stay Calm and Protect Your Data?</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-02/</guid>
      <description>Ransomware has become a major cyber threat to businesses and organizations worldwide. The United States has become the number one target area for ransomware attacks due to the gap between the data protection measures of many local companies and their digital transformation. The complex IT environment brought by the hybrid multi-cloud era has further provided a breeding ground for ransomware. As a result, an unsuspecting ransomware attack can cause unplanned downtime and irreversible damage to business and reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aurreum released the industry&#39;s most reliable cloud data management platform</title>
      <link>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aurreum.com/posts/post-01/</guid>
      <description>The breakout innovator Aurreum International has just released its Cloud Data Protection Service. Built from the ground up by the engineers of Aurreum, the Cloud Data Protection Service aims to bring effective multi-cloud data management tools to IT professionals of small businesses and enterprises. This service will help enterprises effectively protect data in the cloud, avoid data loss, defend against ransomware attacks, and achieve simple and unified cloud data management.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
